Guide to the BOMB Magazine Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Research Material, 1978-2004
  - Printed Material
    - Real Fun, No. 1, 1984 (Box 94)
    - Small Press, The Magazine of Independent Book Publishing
      - Vol. 1, No. 4, 1984 March-April (Box 94)
      - Vol. 1, No. 5, 1984 May-June (Box 94)
    - Wings Over the World Cup, 1982 July (Box 94)
  - Printed Material--General, undated (Box 120)
  - Printed Material--Pamphlet. "Images de la vie quotidienne un ete 89," undated (Box 120)
  - Art--Print. Charles, Michael Ray--Image on a Paper Bag, undated (Box 121)
  - Printed Material--General, undated (Box 121)
  - Art (Box 122)
    - Wegman, William--"Bank/Bar," 1983 (Box 122)
    - Weissman, Benjamin--Sketch with Typed Text from Headless 2004 (Box 122)
  - Printed Material--General, undated (Box 122)
  - Printed Material--General, undated (Box 123)
  - Audio Files (Box 125)
    - Audio Cassettes (Box 125)
    - Micro Cassettes (Box 125)
    - Mini Disks (Box 125)